(Leonard:)personal five-week mission
to do the same.
(Sheldon:)If you want to lure me in with
sexy talk, that's how you do it.
(Penny:)Don't be proud of that.
(Amy:)So, is that a yes?
Not yet. I...
(Sheldon:)How will I learn if
I'm comfortable living with Amy
(Sheldon:)or just comfortable because
I'm in my own apartment?
(Sheldon:)Now, if this experiment
is going to be valid,
(Sheldon:)I suggest a neutral environment.
(Penny:)Well, where would you go?
(Sheldon:)Well, ideally, an enclosed,
(Sheldon:)self-sustaining biodome
in New Mexico.
(Sheldon:)Where we would eat crops
fertilized with our own waste.
And you were worried
about the romance.
(Penny:)Wait.
(Penny:)Why don't you guys stay across
the hall, and we will live here?
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)If my official residence
were across the hall,
(Sheldon:)I wonder if I'd need to knock
every time I came over here.
(Leonard:)That's a good question.
(Leonard:)Maybe just don't come over.
(Sheldon:)Historically, I don't
do well with change.